

## How to reach me:

## My portfolio website:

Softwarepower.ir



#### **Email:**

ahmad.vakil.safir@gmail.com



#### Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/ahmadrezavakila



### Github:

ub AhmadVakil



#### Cell:

+98 904 610 9204

## **SCAN & JUMP TO MY WEBSITE**



### I Can Speak:

English (IELTS 7 - Valid TRF) Swedish (Working proficiency) Farsi (Mother tongue)

### **Personal Profile**

I am a self-driven software and system developer with proficient programming and problem solving skills. I am a team player with significant work experience in Swedish and international companies with relevant academic background.

## **Educational Training**

# Linnéuniversitetet - Växjö, Sweden 2015 - 2018

### Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Network Security (Thesis/Research based)

Academic knowledge in Linux, Java, Python, Assembly, C, C#, JavaScript, web programming, PHP, HTML, CSS, Angular, React, Node.Js, Webpack, Spring Boot, SQL and DBMS, Git, technical communications, IT security policies, Cryptography, Computer networks administration, Penetration testing using Kali Linux and network security.

## Linnéuniversitetet - Växjö, Sweden 2015 - 2016

Higher Education Diploma in Computer Science

## Azad University - Tehran, Iran 2006 - 2009 Association degree in

Association degree in Computer Science

Academic knowledge in Java, C, Pascal, computer networks and fundamental of computer science and electronics. Worked with electronical boards and low level programming languages.

## High school of computer science Tehran, Iran 2003 - 2006

Knowledge in Visual basic, programming fundamental, basic software development, mathematics, physics, and education including preparatory courses required to starting undergraduate academic education.

## **Career Summary**

#### System Developer MegaMiner - Tehran, Iran 2019 - Present

Automation, Designs and develop software solutions.
Develop e-commerce website with hosting control panels such as cPanel, and DirectAdmin.

Develop and integrate rare/unique plugins for our CMS. Prototyping and modifying code to fix errors. Develop backend, Develop Frontend, Design and build UI, fix UX, and integrate several checkouts.

I am also do research and development for the company and help to hire new talents.

#### System Developer Ericsson - Karlskrona, Sweden 2018 - 2019

Telecommunications, Linux,
Java, Python, Groovy, Gerrit, Git,
CI-CD, Jenkins-dsl, Maven,
Gradle, Unit testing, Integration
testing, SonarQube, Mantis
Issue Tracker, code reviews,
vSphere, VMware, AWS, polyth
programming, agile DevOps
methodology, system and full
stack development, REST, Spring
Boot and API.

## IT Manager STNJ - Tehran, Iran 2011 - 2014

Manage the entire network system and computers. Prepare computers and network as required by the staff and support and fix network issues.

### **Professional Skills**

#### **Coding Languages:**

JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python SQL, Java, Node.js, PHP, Kotlin

#### Frameworks/Systems:

MVC, AngularJS, bootstrap

#### E-commerce solutions:

WordPress, Prestashop, Shopify, Plugin developer

#### **Cybersecurity:**

Kali, ethical hacking, strong knowledge in blue and red teams tactics, strong knowledge in cyber attacks and defense solutions. Very good with tools that used to attack or to defend software systems.